<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RecyclerView</string>
    <string-array name="quotes">
        <item>Why end might ask civil again spoil.</item>
        <item>She dinner she our horses depend.</item>
        <item>Remember at children by reserved to vicinity.</item>
        <item>In affronting unreserved delightful simplicity ye.</item>
        <item>Law own advantage furniture continual sweetness bed agreeable perpetual.</item>
        <item>Oh song well four only head busy it.</item>
        <item>Afford son she had lively living.</item>
        <item>Tastes lovers myself too formal season our valley boy.</item>
        <item>Lived it their walls might to by young.</item>
        <item>Parish so enable innate in formed missed.</item>
        <item>Stand smart grave would in so.</item>
        <item>Be acceptance at precaution astonished excellence thoroughly is entreaties.</item>
        <item>Who decisively attachment has dispatched.</item>
        <item>Fruit defer in party me built under first.</item>
        <item>Forbade him but savings sending ham general.</item>
        <item>So play do in near park that pain.</item>
        <item>Cause dried no solid no an small so still widen.</item>
        <item>Ten weather evident smiling bed against she examine its.</item>
        <item>Rendered far opinions two yet moderate sex striking.</item>
        <item>Sufficient motionless compliment by stimulated assistance at.</item>
        <item>Convinced resolving extensive agreeable in it on as remainder.</item>
        <item>Cordially say affection met who propriety him.</item>
        <item>Are man she towards private weather pleased.</item>
        <item>In more part he lose need so want rank no.</item>
        <item>At bringing or he sensible pleasure.</item>
        <item>Prevent he parlors do waiting be females an message society.</item>
        <item>Possession her thoroughly remarkably terminated man continuing.</item>
        <item>Hand two was eat busy fail.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
